[
  {
    "rank": "1",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE HORSE-LIKE ANIMAL WITH BLACK AND WHITE STRIPES?",
    "answer": "ZEBRA",
    "percentage": "93.30",
    "response_time": "6.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "2",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LONG SLEEP SOME ANIMALS GO THROUGH DURING THE ENTIRE WINTER?",
    "answer": "HIBERNATION",
    "percentage": "89.00",
    "response_time": "9.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "3",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RUBBER OBJECT THAT IS HIT BACK AND FORTH BY HOCKEY PLAYERS?",
    "answer": "PUCK",
    "percentage": "88.80",
    "response_time": "6.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "4",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE REMAINS OF PLANTS AND ANIMALS THAT ARE FOUND IN STONE?",
    "answer": "FOSSILS",
    "percentage": "87.30",
    "response_time": "9.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "5",
    "question": "WHICH PRECIOUS GEM IS RED?",
    "answer": "RUBY",
    "percentage": "84.90",
    "response_time": "4.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "6",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SEVERE HEADACHE THAT RETURNS PERIODICALLY AND OFTEN IS ACCOMPANIED BY NAUSEA?",
    "answer": "MIGRAINE",
    "percentage": "84.70",
    "response_time": "10.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "7",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “ROMEO AND JULIET”?",
    "answer": "SHAKESPEARE",
    "percentage": "84.30",
    "response_time": "10.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "8",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A DRIED GRAPE?",
    "answer": "RAISIN",
    "percentage": "83.50",
    "response_time": "6.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "9",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COMIC STRIP CHARACTER WHO EATS SPINACH TO INCREASE HIS STRENGTH?",
    "answer": "POPEYE",
    "percentage": "82.40",
    "response_time": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "10",
    "question": "WHAT ANIMAL RUNS THE FASTEST?",
    "answer": "CHEETAH",
    "percentage": "81.60",
    "response_time": "5.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "11",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PROCESS BY WHICH PLANTS MAKE THEIR FOOD?",
    "answer": "PHOTOSYNTHESIS",
    "percentage": "80.00",
    "response_time": "11.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "12",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF DOROTHY’S DOG IN “THE WIZARD OF OZ”?",
    "answer": "TOTO",
    "percentage": "79.90",
    "response_time": "6.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "13",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOLTEN ROCK THAT RUNS DOWN THE SIDE OF A VOLCANO DURING AN ERUPTION?",
    "answer": "LAVA",
    "percentage": "79.30",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "14",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE SUPPOSEDLY UNSINKABLE SHIP THAT SUNK ON ITS MAIDEN VOYAGE IN 1912?",
    "answer": "TITANIC",
    "percentage": "78.90",
    "response_time": "9.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "15",
    "question": "WHICH SPORT USES THE TERMS “GUTTER” AND “ALLEY”?",
    "answer": "BOWLING",
    "percentage": "78.80",
    "response_time": "6.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "16",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A GIANT OCEAN WAVE CAUSED BY AN EARTHQUAKE?",
    "answer": "TSUNAMI",
    "percentage": "78.40",
    "response_time": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "17",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE TERM FOR HITTING A VOLLEYBALL DOWN HARD INTO THE OPPONENT’S COURT?",
    "answer": "SPIKE",
    "percentage": "78.40",
    "response_time": "7.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "18",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE VILLAINOUS CAPTAIN IN THE STORY “PETER PAN”?",
    "answer": "HOOK",
    "percentage": "78.10",
    "response_time": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "19",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF TARZAN’S GIRLFRIEND?",
    "answer": "JANE",
    "percentage": "78.10",
    "response_time": "4.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "20",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BROTHERS WHO FLEW THE FIRST AIRPLANE AT KITTY HAWK?",
    "answer": "WRIGHT",
    "percentage": "75.10",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "21",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A MEDICAL DOCTOR WHO SPECIALIZES IN CUTTING THE BODY?",
    "answer": "SURGEON",
    "percentage": "74.80",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "22",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO SET FOOT ON THE MOON?",
    "answer": "ARMSTRONG",
    "percentage": "74.10",
    "response_time": "11"
  },
  {
    "rank": "23",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF FRANCE?",
    "answer": "PARIS",
    "percentage": "73.00",
    "response_time": "5.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "24",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CRIME IN WHICH A BUILDING OR PROPERTY IS PURPOSELY SET ON FIRE?",
    "answer": "ARSON",
    "percentage": "72.20",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "25",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHORT PLEATED SKIRT WORN BY MEN IN SCOTLAND?",
    "answer": "KILT",
    "percentage": "71.70",
    "response_time": "6.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "26",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN INABILITY TO SLEEP?",
    "answer": "INSOMNIA",
    "percentage": "71.40",
    "response_time": "7.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "27",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A MEDICAL DOCTOR WHO SPECIALIZES IN DISEASES OF THE SKIN?",
    "answer": "DERMATOLOGIST",
    "percentage": "69.20",
    "response_time": "12.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "28",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST OCEAN ON EARTH?",
    "answer": "PACIFIC",
    "percentage": "68.50",
    "response_time": "8.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "29",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHIP THAT CARRIED THE PILGRIMS TO AMERICA IN 1620?",
    "answer": "MAYFLOWER",
    "percentage": "66.30",
    "response_time": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "30",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A CYCLONE THAT OCCURS OVER LAND?",
    "answer": "TORNADO",
    "percentage": "64.10",
    "response_time": "8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "31",
    "question": "WHICH SPORT IS ASSOCIATED WITH WIMBLEDON?",
    "answer": "TENNIS",
    "percentage": "61.90",
    "response_time": "5.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "32",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BIRD THAT CANNOT FLY AND IS THE LARGEST BIRD ON EARTH?",
    "answer": "OSTRICH",
    "percentage": "60.30",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "33",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ISLAND-CITY BELIEVED SINCE ANTIQUITY TO HAVE SUNK INTO THE OCEAN?",
    "answer": "ATLANTIS",
    "percentage": "59.30",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "34",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIZARD THAT CHANGES ITS COLOR TO MATCH THE SURROUNDINGS?",
    "answer": "CHAMELEON",
    "percentage": "58.90",
    "response_time": "11.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "35",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE THICK LAYER OF FAT ON A WHALE?",
    "answer": "BLUBBER",
    "percentage": "57.20",
    "response_time": "6.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "36",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WHO HAD THE MOST HOME RUNS IN A SINGLE SEASON PRIOR TO 1961?",
    "answer": "RUTH",
    "percentage": "56.80",
    "response_time": "12.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "37",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A YOUNG SHEEP?",
    "answer": "LAMB",
    "percentage": "56.10",
    "response_time": "7.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "38",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LARGEST PLANET IN THE SOLAR SYSTEM?",
    "answer": "JUPITER",
    "percentage": "55.90",
    "response_time": "8.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "39",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NAVIGATION INSTRUMENT USED AT SEA TO PLOT POSITION RELATIVE TO THE MAGNETIC NORTH POLE?",
    "answer": "COMPASS",
    "percentage": "52.60",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "40",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE TERM IN GOLF REFERRING TO A SCORE OF ONE UNDER PAR ON A PARTICULAR HOLE?",
    "answer": "BIRDIE",
    "percentage": "52.30",
    "response_time": "12.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "41",
    "question": "WHICH GAME USES A RUBBER BALL AND LITTLE METAL PIECES?",
    "answer": "JACKS",
    "percentage": "52.10",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "42",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A DRIED PLUM?",
    "answer": "PRUNE",
    "percentage": "51.70",
    "response_time": "7.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "43",
    "question": "IN WHICH SPORT DOES A RIDER ON HORSEBACK HIT A BALL WITH HIS MALLET?",
    "answer": "POLO",
    "percentage": "51.00",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "44",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LEGENDARY ONE-EYED GIANT IN GREEK MYTHOLOGY?",
    "answer": "CYCLOPS",
    "percentage": "50.70",
    "response_time": "9.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "45",
    "question": "IN WHAT PARK IS “OLD FAITHFUL” LOCATED?",
    "answer": "YELLOWSTONE",
    "percentage": "49.10",
    "response_time": "9.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "46",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE POKER HAND IN WHICH ALL OF THE CARDS ARE OF THE SAME SUIT?",
    "answer": "FLUSH",
    "percentage": "48.60",
    "response_time": "14.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "47",
    "question": "IN WHICH SPORT IS THE STANLEY CUP AWARDED?",
    "answer": "HOCKEY",
    "percentage": "48.10",
    "response_time": "5.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "48",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CHAPEL WHOSE CEILING WAS PAINTED BY MICHELANGELO?",
    "answer": "SISTINE",
    "percentage": "47.50",
    "response_time": "12.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "49",
    "question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BAGHDAD THE CAPITAL?",
    "answer": "IRAQ",
    "percentage": "46.80",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "50",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIQUID PORTION OF WHOLE BLOOD?",
    "answer": "PLASMA",
    "percentage": "46.80",
    "response_time": "10.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "51",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CITY IN ITALY THAT IS KNOWN FOR ITS CANALS?",
    "answer": "VENICE",
    "percentage": "45.90",
    "response_time": "9.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "52",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SPEAR LIKE OBJECT THAT IS THROWN DURING A TRACK MEET?",
    "answer": "JAVELIN",
    "percentage": "45.20",
    "response_time": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "53",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO RODE HORSEBACK IN 1775 TO WARN THAT THE BRITISH WERE COMING?",
    "answer": "REVERE",
    "percentage": "44.30",
    "response_time": "13.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "54",
    "question": "WHO WAS THE EGYPTIAN QUEEN WHO JOINED FORCES WITH MARK ANTONY OF ROME?",
    "answer": "CLEOPATRA",
    "percentage": "44.30",
    "response_time": "11"
  },
  {
    "rank": "55",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO ASSASSINATED ABRAHAM LINCOLN?",
    "answer": "BOOTH",
    "percentage": "43.80",
    "response_time": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "56",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SHOWED THAT LIGHTNING IS ELECTRIC?",
    "answer": "FRANKLIN",
    "percentage": "43.70",
    "response_time": "11.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "57",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FAMOUS MAGICIAN AND ESCAPE ARTIST WHO DIED OF APPENDICITIS?",
    "answer": "HOUDINI",
    "percentage": "43.60",
    "response_time": "12.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "58",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF DEER MEAT?",
    "answer": "VENISON",
    "percentage": "43.20",
    "response_time": "10.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "59",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGE HAIRY SPIDER THAT LIVES NEAR BANANAS?",
    "answer": "TARANTULA",
    "percentage": "42.90",
    "response_time": "13.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "60",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE OCEAN THAT IS LOCATED BETWEEN AFRICA AND AUSTRALIA?",
    "answer": "INDIAN",
    "percentage": "42.70",
    "response_time": "12.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "61",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHO RECORDED “HEARTBREAK HOTEL” AND “ALL SHOOK UP”?",
    "answer": "PRESLEY",
    "percentage": "42.40",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "62",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CRIME IN WHICH A PERSON PURPOSELY BETRAYS HIS COUNTRY?",
    "answer": "TREASON",
    "percentage": "41.80",
    "response_time": "12"
  },
  {
    "rank": "63",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FIRST ARTIFICIAL SATELLITE PUT IN ORBIT BY RUSSIA IN 1957?",
    "answer": "SPUTNIK",
    "percentage": "41.70",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "64",
    "question": "WHAT BRAND OF CIGARETTE WAS FIRST TO HAVE THE FLIP-TOP BOX?",
    "answer": "MARLBORO",
    "percentage": "39.90",
    "response_time": "10.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "65",
    "question": "WHAT KIND OF METAL IS ASSOCIATED WITH A 50TH WEDDING ANNIVERSARY?",
    "answer": "GOLD",
    "percentage": "39.60",
    "response_time": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "66",
    "question": "WHICH TYPE OF SNAKE DO ASIAN SNAKE-CHARMERS USE?",
    "answer": "COBRA",
    "percentage": "39.10",
    "response_time": "9.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "67",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE ONLY LIQUID METAL AT ROOM TEMPERATURE?",
    "answer": "MERCURY",
    "percentage": "38.80",
    "response_time": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "68",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE DESERT PEOPLE WHO WANDER INSTEAD OF LIVING IN ONE PLACE?",
    "answer": "NOMADS",
    "percentage": "35.20",
    "response_time": "12.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "69",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF NEW YORK?",
    "answer": "ALBANY",
    "percentage": "33.10",
    "response_time": "12.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "70",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ORGAN THAT PRODUCES INSULIN?",
    "answer": "PANCREAS",
    "percentage": "32.70",
    "response_time": "13.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "71",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COLLAR BONE?",
    "answer": "CLAVICLE",
    "percentage": "32.40",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "72",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE EXTINCT REPTILES KNOWN AS “TERRIBLE LIZARDS”?",
    "answer": "DINOSAURS",
    "percentage": "31.50",
    "response_time": "11.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "73",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF RUSSIA?",
    "answer": "MOSCOW",
    "percentage": "30.90",
    "response_time": "7.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "74",
    "question": "WHICH BREED OF CAT HAS BLUE EYES?",
    "answer": "SIAMESE",
    "percentage": "30.80",
    "response_time": "9.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "75",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SECOND U.S. PRESIDENT?",
    "answer": "ADAMS",
    "percentage": "30.30",
    "response_time": "10"
  },
  {
    "rank": "76",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CONSTELLATION THAT LOOKS LIKE A FLYING HORSE?",
    "answer": "PEGASUS",
    "percentage": "30.00",
    "response_time": "9.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "77",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE KIND OF CAT THAT SPOKE TO ALICE IN THE STORY “ALICE’S ADVENTURES IN WONDERLAND”?",
    "answer": "CHESHIRE",
    "percentage": "30.00",
    "response_time": "10.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "78",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO PROPOSED THE THEORY OF RELATIVITY?",
    "answer": "EINSTEIN",
    "percentage": "29.70",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "79",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO SUPPOSEDLY DESIGNED AND SEWED THE FIRST AMERICAN FLAG?",
    "answer": "ROSS",
    "percentage": "28.60",
    "response_time": "8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "80",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST SIGNER OF THE “DECLARATION OF INDEPENDENCE”?",
    "answer": "HANCOCK",
    "percentage": "28.50",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "81",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF KING ARTHUR’S SWORD?",
    "answer": "EXCALIBUR",
    "percentage": "28.50",
    "response_time": "10"
  },
  {
    "rank": "82",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE WORD THAT MEANS A NAUTICAL MILE PER HOUR?",
    "answer": "KNOT",
    "percentage": "27.70",
    "response_time": "11.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "83",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR THE ASTRONOMICAL BODIES THAT ENTER THE EARTH’S ATMOSPHERE?",
    "answer": "METEORS",
    "percentage": "27.10",
    "response_time": "14.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "84",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LONGEST RIVER IN SOUTH AMERICA?",
    "answer": "AMAZON",
    "percentage": "26.70",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "85",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AUTOMOBILE INSTRUMENT THAT MEASURES MILEAGE?",
    "answer": "ODOMETER",
    "percentage": "25.80",
    "response_time": "13.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "86",
    "question": "WHAT ITALIAN CITY WAS DESTROYED WHEN MOUNT VESUVIUS ERUPTED IN 79 A.D.?",
    "answer": "POMPEII",
    "percentage": "25.80",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "87",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF BATMAN’S SECRET IDENTITY IN THE BATMAN COMICS?",
    "answer": "WAYNE",
    "percentage": "25.20",
    "response_time": "11"
  },
  {
    "rank": "88",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MYTHICAL GIANT LUMBERJACK?",
    "answer": "BUNYAN",
    "percentage": "24.50",
    "response_time": "14.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "89",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COMPANY THAT PRODUCES “BABY RUTH” CANDY BARS?",
    "answer": "NESTLE",
    "percentage": "24.50",
    "response_time": "10.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "90",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF SOCRATES’ MOST FAMOUS STUDENT?",
    "answer": "PLATO",
    "percentage": "23.90",
    "response_time": "14.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "91",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE THREE-LEAF CLOVER THAT IS THE EMBLEM OF IRELAND?",
    "answer": "SHAMROCK",
    "percentage": "23.90",
    "response_time": "10.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "92",
    "question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BUENOS AIRES THE CAPITAL?",
    "answer": "ARGENTINA",
    "percentage": "20.40",
    "response_time": "10.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "93",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTRESS WHO RECEIVED THE BEST ACTRESS AWARD FOR THE MOVIE “MARY POPPINS”?",
    "answer": "ANDREWS",
    "percentage": "20.30",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "94",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOUNTAIN RANGE IN WHICH MOUNT EVEREST IS LOCATED?",
    "answer": "HIMALAYAS",
    "percentage": "19.80",
    "response_time": "13.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "95",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE UNIT OF SOUND INTENSITY?",
    "answer": "DECIBEL",
    "percentage": "19.00",
    "response_time": "8.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "96",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PROJECT WHICH DEVELOPED THE ATOMIC BOMB DURING WORLD WAR II?",
    "answer": "MANHATTAN",
    "percentage": "18.80",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "97",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE UNIT OF ELECTRICAL POWER THAT REFERS TO A CURRENT OF ONE AMPERE AT ONE VOLT?",
    "answer": "WATT",
    "percentage": "18.70",
    "response_time": "12.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "98",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF THE BOOK “1984”?",
    "answer": "ORWELL",
    "percentage": "18.50",
    "response_time": "12.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "99",
    "question": "IN WHICH GAME ARE MEN CROWNED?",
    "answer": "CHECKERS",
    "percentage": "17.60",
    "response_time": "12.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "100",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO ASSASSINATED PRESIDENT JOHN F. KENNEDY?",
    "answer": "OSWALD",
    "percentage": "17.20",
    "response_time": "14.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "101",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF BATMAN’S BUTLER?",
    "answer": "ALFRED",
    "percentage": "16.30",
    "response_time": "11.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "102",
    "question": "WHICH COUNTRY WAS THE FIRST TO USE GUNPOWDER?",
    "answer": "CHINA",
    "percentage": "16.00",
    "response_time": "8.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "103",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN AIRPLANE WITHOUT AN ENGINE?",
    "answer": "GLIDER",
    "percentage": "15.70",
    "response_time": "11.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "104",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NORTH STAR?",
    "answer": "POLARIS",
    "percentage": "15.60",
    "response_time": "6.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "105",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE ONLY WORD THAT THE RAVEN SAYS IN EDGAR ALLEN POE’S POEM “THE RAVEN”?",
    "answer": "NEVERMORE",
    "percentage": "15.50",
    "response_time": "11.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "106",
    "question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE YEN THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "answer": "JAPAN",
    "percentage": "15.20",
    "response_time": "7.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "107",
    "question": "IN WHAT EUROPEAN CITY IS THE PARTHENON LOCATED?",
    "answer": "ATHENS",
    "percentage": "15.00",
    "response_time": "8.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "108",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FURRY ANIMAL THAT ATTACKS COBRA SNAKES?",
    "answer": "MONGOOSE",
    "percentage": "14.90",
    "response_time": "8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "109",
    "question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE RUPEE THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "answer": "INDIA",
    "percentage": "14.70",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "110",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO FIRST STUDIED GENETIC INHERITANCE IN PLANTS?",
    "answer": "MENDEL",
    "percentage": "14.40",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "111",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE “STAR SPANGLED BANNER”?",
    "answer": "KEY",
    "percentage": "14.10",
    "response_time": "8.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "112",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PALACE IN LONDON IN WHICH THE MONARCH OF ENGLAND RESIDES?",
    "answer": "BUCKINGHAM",
    "percentage": "14.10",
    "response_time": "16"
  },
  {
    "rank": "113",
    "question": "IN WHICH GAME ARE THE STANDARD PIECES OF STAUNTON DESIGN?",
    "answer": "CHESS",
    "percentage": "13.80",
    "response_time": "14.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "114",
    "question": "WHAT ARE PEOPLE WHO MAKE MAPS CALLED?",
    "answer": "CARTOGRAPHERS",
    "percentage": "13.80",
    "response_time": "9.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "115",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE ZEPPELIN THAT EXPLODED IN LAKEHURST N.J. IN 1937?",
    "answer": "HINDENBURG",
    "percentage": "13.40",
    "response_time": "20.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "116",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE PALACE BUILT IN FRANCE BY KING LOUIS XIV?",
    "answer": "VERSAILLES",
    "percentage": "12.80",
    "response_time": "10.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "117",
    "question": "IN WHICH CITY IS THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY LOCATED?",
    "answer": "ANNAPOLIS",
    "percentage": "12.70",
    "response_time": "11.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "118",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIGHTEST WOOD KNOWN?",
    "answer": "BALSA",
    "percentage": "12.50",
    "response_time": "9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "119",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO LATER BECAME KNOWN AS MUHAMMAD ALI?",
    "answer": "CLAY",
    "percentage": "11.70",
    "response_time": "10.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "120",
    "question": "WHAT ISLAND IS THE LARGEST IN THE WORLD EXCLUDING AUSTRALIA?",
    "answer": "GREENLAND",
    "percentage": "11.10",
    "response_time": "15.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "121",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SMALL JAPANESE STOVE USED FOR OUTDOOR COOKING?",
    "answer": "HIBACHI",
    "percentage": "11.00",
    "response_time": "11.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "122",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO BEGAN THE PROFESSION OF NURSING?",
    "answer": "NIGHTINGALE",
    "percentage": "10.80",
    "response_time": "13.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "123",
    "question": "WHO WAS THE LEADER OF THE ARGONAUTS?",
    "answer": "JASON",
    "percentage": "10.70",
    "response_time": "5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "124",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “GUERNICA”?",
    "answer": "PICASSO",
    "percentage": "10.70",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "125",
    "question": "IN WHAT ANCIENT CITY WERE THE “HANGING GARDENS” LOCATED?",
    "answer": "BABYLON",
    "percentage": "10.30",
    "response_time": "16.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "126",
    "question": "WHAT ARE PEOPLE CALLED WHO EXPLORE CAVES?",
    "answer": "SPELUNKERS",
    "percentage": "10.00",
    "response_time": "14.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "127",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CAPTAIN OF THE PEQUOD IN THE BOOK “MOBY DICK”?",
    "answer": "AHAB",
    "percentage": "9.700",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "128",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF KENTUCKY?",
    "answer": "FRANKFORT",
    "percentage": "9.500",
    "response_time": "18.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "129",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN ILLEGAL MOVE BY A BASEBALL PITCHER THAT RESULTS IN ALL RUNNERS ADVANCING ONE BASE?",
    "answer": "BALK",
    "percentage": "9.300",
    "response_time": "10"
  },
  {
    "rank": "130",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AMERICAN WHO STARRED IN THE 1936 OLYMPICS?",
    "answer": "OWENS",
    "percentage": "9.300",
    "response_time": "12.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "131",
    "question": "THE DEEPEST PART OF THE OCEAN IS LOCATED AT WHICH TRENCH?",
    "answer": "MARIANA",
    "percentage": "9.300",
    "response_time": "11.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "132",
    "question": "WHICH SPORT USES THE TERMS “STONES” AND “BROOMS”?",
    "answer": "CURLING",
    "percentage": "9.200",
    "response_time": "19.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "133",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE PROPER NAME FOR A BADMINTON BIRD?",
    "answer": "SHUTTLECOCK",
    "percentage": "9.100",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "134",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “OLIVER TWIST”?",
    "answer": "DICKENS",
    "percentage": "9.000",
    "response_time": "9.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "135",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF DELAWARE?",
    "answer": "DOVER",
    "percentage": "9.000",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "136",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED THE PHONOGRAPH?",
    "answer": "EDISON",
    "percentage": "8.600",
    "response_time": "15.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "137",
    "question": "IN WHICH TYPE OF SKI RACE DOES THE DOWNHILL SKIER MAKE SHARP TURNS AROUND POLES?",
    "answer": "SLALOM",
    "percentage": "8.600",
    "response_time": "14.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "138",
    "question": "IN WHICH CITY IS HEATHROW AIRPORT LOCATED?",
    "answer": "LONDON",
    "percentage": "8.300",
    "response_time": "8.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "139",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF JAMAICA?",
    "answer": "KINGSTON",
    "percentage": "8.100",
    "response_time": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "140",
    "question": "WHICH PLANET WAS THE LAST TO BE DISCOVERED?",
    "answer": "NEPTUNE",
    "percentage": "8.000",
    "response_time": "18.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "141",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE MURDERS IN THE RUE MORGUE”?",
    "answer": "POE",
    "percentage": "8.000",
    "response_time": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "142",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHIP ON WHICH CHARLES DARWIN MADE HIS SCIENTIFIC VOYAGE?",
    "answer": "BEAGLE",
    "percentage": "7.900",
    "response_time": "10.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "143",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF CHILE?",
    "answer": "SANTIAGO",
    "percentage": "7.700",
    "response_time": "15.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "144",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE OLD MAN AND THE SEA”?",
    "answer": "HEMINGWAY",
    "percentage": "7.700",
    "response_time": "8.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "145",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE “CANTERBURY TALES”?",
    "answer": "CHAUCER",
    "percentage": "7.600",
    "response_time": "10.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "146",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FOUNTAIN IN ROME INTO WHICH COINS ARE THROWN FOR GOOD LUCK?",
    "answer": "TREVI",
    "percentage": "7.100",
    "response_time": "24.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "147",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS PRESIDENT DIRECTLY AFTER JAMES MADISON?",
    "answer": "MONROE",
    "percentage": "6.800",
    "response_time": "11.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "148",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ASTRONOMER WHO PUBLISHED IN 1543 HIS THEORY THAT THE EARTH REVOLVES AROUND THE SUN?",
    "answer": "COPERNICUS",
    "percentage": "6.700",
    "response_time": "15"
  },
  {
    "rank": "149",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CRIMINAL WHO WAS KNOWN AS “SCARFACE”?",
    "answer": "CAPONE",
    "percentage": "6.600",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "150",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LONE RANGER’S INDIAN SIDEKICK?",
    "answer": "TONTO",
    "percentage": "6.100",
    "response_time": "7.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "151",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF DENMARK?",
    "answer": "COPENHAGEN",
    "percentage": "6.000",
    "response_time": "23.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "152",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS THE RADIO BROADCASTER FOR THE “WAR OF THE WORLDS”?",
    "answer": "WELLES",
    "percentage": "5.900",
    "response_time": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "153",
    "question": "IN WHICH CITY IS MICHELANGELO’S STATUE OF DAVID LOCATED?",
    "answer": "FLORENCE",
    "percentage": "5.800",
    "response_time": "14.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "154",
    "question": "WHAT WAS FRANK LLOYD WRIGHT’S PROFESSION?",
    "answer": "ARCHITECT",
    "percentage": "5.800",
    "response_time": "7.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "155",
    "question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS NAIROBI THE CAPITAL?",
    "answer": "KENYA",
    "percentage": "5.300",
    "response_time": "6.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "156",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE HILLBILLY FAMILY THAT HAD A FAMOUS FEUD WITH THE MCCOY FAMILY?",
    "answer": "HATFIELD",
    "percentage": "5.200",
    "response_time": "12.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "157",
    "question": "WHAT KIND OF POISON DID SOCRATES TAKE AS HIS EXECUTION?",
    "answer": "HEMLOCK",
    "percentage": "5.200",
    "response_time": "7.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "158",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO COMPLETE A SOLO FLIGHT ACROSS THE ATLANTIC OCEAN?",
    "answer": "LINDBERGH",
    "percentage": "5.200",
    "response_time": "15.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "159",
    "question": "ANDY GRIFFITH WAS THE SHERIFF OF WHAT TOWN ON TELEVISION’S “ANDY GRIFFITH SHOW”?",
    "answer": "MAYBERRY",
    "percentage": "5.200",
    "response_time": "9.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "160",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ROMAN EMPEROR WHO FIDDLED WHILE ROME BURNED?",
    "answer": "NERO",
    "percentage": "5.200",
    "response_time": "10.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "161",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CITY IN WHICH THE BASEBALL HALL OF FAME IS LOCATED?",
    "answer": "COOPERSTOWN",
    "percentage": "5.100",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "162",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE UNIT OF MEASURE THAT REFERS TO A SIX-FOOT DEPTH OF WATER?",
    "answer": "FATHOM",
    "percentage": "5.100",
    "response_time": "19.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "163",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SCIENTIST WHO DISCOVERED RADIUM?",
    "answer": "CURIE",
    "percentage": "4.600",
    "response_time": "8.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "164",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “BRAVE NEW WORLD”?",
    "answer": "HUXLEY",
    "percentage": "4.500",
    "response_time": "10.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "165",
    "question": "IN ADDITION TO THE KENTUCKY DERBY AND THE BELMONT STAKES WHAT HORSE RACE COMPRISES THE TRIPLE CROWN?",
    "answer": "PREAKNESS",
    "percentage": "4.400",
    "response_time": "21"
  },
  {
    "rank": "166",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CRIMINAL WHO WAS KILLED BY FBI AGENTS OUTSIDE OF A CHICAGO MOVIE THEATER?",
    "answer": "DILLINGER",
    "percentage": "4.400",
    "response_time": "17.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "167",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SINGER WHO POPULARIZED A DANCE KNOWN AS THE “TWIST”?",
    "answer": "CHECKER",
    "percentage": "4.100",
    "response_time": "21.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "168",
    "question": "OVER WHICH RIVER IS THE GEORGE WASHINGTON BRIDGE?",
    "answer": "HUDSON",
    "percentage": "4.100",
    "response_time": "32.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "169",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED DYNAMITE?",
    "answer": "NOBEL",
    "percentage": "4.000",
    "response_time": "7.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "170",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CHINESE RELIGION FOUNDED BY LAO TSE?",
    "answer": "TAOISM",
    "percentage": "4.000",
    "response_time": "13"
  },
  {
    "rank": "171",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMMANDER WHO LOST THE BATTLE OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN RIVER?",
    "answer": "CUSTER",
    "percentage": "3.800",
    "response_time": "11"
  },
  {
    "rank": "172",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NAVIGATION INSTRUMENT USED AT SEA TO PLOT POSITION BY THE STARS?",
    "answer": "SEXTANT",
    "percentage": "3.800",
    "response_time": "14.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "173",
    "question": "WHO WAS THE MOST FAMOUS GREEK DOCTOR?",
    "answer": "HIPPOCRATES",
    "percentage": "3.700",
    "response_time": "16.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "174",
    "question": "IN WHICH CITY DOES THE COTTON BOWL TAKE PLACE?",
    "answer": "DALLAS",
    "percentage": "3.700",
    "response_time": "10.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "175",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE THE SHERLOCK HOLMES STORIES?",
    "answer": "DOYLE",
    "percentage": "3.600",
    "response_time": "17"
  },
  {
    "rank": "176",
    "question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE DRACHMA THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "answer": "GREECE",
    "percentage": "3.600",
    "response_time": "19.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "177",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MANSION IN VIRGINIA THAT WAS THOMAS JEFFERSON’S HOME?",
    "answer": "MONTICELLO",
    "percentage": "3.500",
    "response_time": "11.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "178",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LONGEST RIVER IN ASIA?",
    "answer": "YANGTZE",
    "percentage": "3.500",
    "response_time": "17.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "179",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO RECEIVED THE BEST ACTOR AWARD FOR THE MOVIE “ON THE WATERFRONT”?",
    "answer": "BRANDO",
    "percentage": "3.400",
    "response_time": "11.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "180",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MALE STAR OF THE MOVIE “CASABLANCA”?",
    "answer": "BOGART",
    "percentage": "3.400",
    "response_time": "9.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "181",
    "question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BUDAPEST THE CAPITAL?",
    "answer": "HUNGARY",
    "percentage": "3.300",
    "response_time": "9.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "182",
    "question": "WHO IS KNOWN AS “THE FATHER OF GEOMETRY”?",
    "answer": "EUCLID",
    "percentage": "3.300",
    "response_time": "20.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "183",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE HUSBAND-WIFE SPIES WHO WERE ELECTROCUTED IN 1951 FOR PASSING ATOMIC SECRETS TO RUSSIA?",
    "answer": "ROSENBERG",
    "percentage": "3.100",
    "response_time": "29"
  },
  {
    "rank": "184",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMPOSER WHO WROTE THE OPERA “DON GIOVANNI”?",
    "answer": "MOZART",
    "percentage": "3.000",
    "response_time": "10.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "185",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF THE JAMES BOND NOVELS?",
    "answer": "FLEMING",
    "percentage": "3.000",
    "response_time": "11.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "186",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF BUFFALO BILL?",
    "answer": "CODY",
    "percentage": "3.000",
    "response_time": "14.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "187",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE UNDER THE PSEUDONYM OF MARK TWAIN?",
    "answer": "CLEMENS",
    "percentage": "2.900",
    "response_time": "15.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "188",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ISLAND ON WHICH NAPOLEON WAS BORN?",
    "answer": "CORSICA",
    "percentage": "2.900",
    "response_time": "38.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "189",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DOCTOR WHO FIRST DEVELOPED A VACCINE AGAINST POLIO?",
    "answer": "SALK",
    "percentage": "2.800",
    "response_time": "16.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "190",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO BEGAN THE REFORMATION IN GERMANY?",
    "answer": "LUTHER",
    "percentage": "2.800",
    "response_time": "18.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "191",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF FINLAND?",
    "answer": "HELSINKI",
    "percentage": "2.600",
    "response_time": "14"
  },
  {
    "rank": "192",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE APOLLO LUNAR MODULE THAT LANDED THE FIRST MAN ON THE MOON?",
    "answer": "EAGLE",
    "percentage": "2.500",
    "response_time": "30.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "193",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COSMONAUT WHO WAS THE FIRST PERSON TO ORBIT AROUND THE EARTH?",
    "answer": "GAGARIN",
    "percentage": "2.400",
    "response_time": "10.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "194",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF ROY ROGER’S DOG?",
    "answer": "BULLET",
    "percentage": "2.100",
    "response_time": "8.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "195",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF ALEXANDER GRAHAM BELL’S ASSISTANT?",
    "answer": "WATSON",
    "percentage": "2.100",
    "response_time": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "196",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMPOSER OF THE “MAPLE LEAF RAG”?",
    "answer": "JOPLIN",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "197",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE PLAYWRIGHT WHO WROTE “A STREETCAR NAMED DESIRE”?",
    "answer": "WILLIAMS",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "26.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "198",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “LITTLE WOMEN”?",
    "answer": "ALCOTT",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "6.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "199",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO CLIMB MOUNT EVEREST?",
    "answer": "HILLARY",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "8.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "200",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PLAYED RHETT BUTLER IN “GONE WITH THE WIND”?",
    "answer": "GABLE",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "22.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "201",
    "question": "IN WHICH COUNTRY IS ANGEL FALLS LOCATED?",
    "answer": "VENEZUELA",
    "percentage": "2.000",
    "response_time": "17.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "202",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF CANADA?",
    "answer": "OTTAWA",
    "percentage": "1.900",
    "response_time": "18.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "203",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE TWENTY-FIRST U.S. PRESIDENT?",
    "answer": "ARTHUR",
    "percentage": "1.900",
    "response_time": "26.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "204",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE GOLDFISH IN THE STORY OF PINOCCHIO?",
    "answer": "CLEO",
    "percentage": "1.900",
    "response_time": "16"
  },
  {
    "rank": "205",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE VILLAINOUS PEOPLE WHO LIVED UNDERGROUND IN H. G. WELLS’S BOOK “THE TIME MACHINE”?",
    "answer": "MORLOCKS",
    "percentage": "1.800",
    "response_time": "19.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "206",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE CHARACTER PORTRAYED BY ROBERT STACK ON THE TELEVISION SHOW “THE UNTOUCHABLES”?",
    "answer": "NESS",
    "percentage": "1.500",
    "response_time": "11.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "207",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF AUSTRALIA?",
    "answer": "CANBERRA",
    "percentage": "1.500",
    "response_time": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "208",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “THE PERSISTENCE OF MEMORY”?",
    "answer": "DALI",
    "percentage": "1.500",
    "response_time": "16"
  },
  {
    "rank": "209",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED THE TELEGRAPH?",
    "answer": "MORSE",
    "percentage": "1.400",
    "response_time": "9.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "210",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RIVER ON WHICH BONN IS LOCATED?",
    "answer": "RHINE",
    "percentage": "1.400",
    "response_time": "17.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "211",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SUBSTANCE DERIVED FROM A WHALE THAT IS USED TO MAKE PERFUME?",
    "answer": "AMBERGRIS",
    "percentage": "1.400",
    "response_time": "41.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "212",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "percentage": "NaN",
    "response_time": "143"
  },
  {
    "rank": "213",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE CLOWN ON THE “HOWDY DOODY” TELEVISION SHOW?",
    "answer": "CLARABELL",
    "percentage": "1.400",
    "response_time": "24.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "214",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF DAGWOOD’S BOSS IN THE COMIC STRIP “BLONDIE”?",
    "answer": "DITHERS",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "9.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "215",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MOVIE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED SPARTACUS?",
    "answer": "DOUGLAS",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "7.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "216",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO FOUNDED THE AMERICAN RED CROSS?",
    "answer": "BARTON",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "14.1"
  },
  {
    "rank": "217",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE UNION GENERAL WHO DEFEATED THE CONFEDERATE ARMY AT THE CIVIL WAR BATTLE OF GETTYSBURG?",
    "answer": "MEADE",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "16.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "218",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AVENUE THAT IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWS ATLANTIC AVENUE IN THE GAME OF MONOPOLY?",
    "answer": "VENTNOR",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "31.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "219",
    "question": "WHICH GAME USES A DOUBLING CUBE?",
    "answer": "BACKGAMMON",
    "percentage": "1.000",
    "response_time": "26.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "220",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SUPPOSEDLY KILLED JESSE JAMES?",
    "answer": "FORD",
    "percentage": "0.9000",
    "response_time": "9.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "221",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE EUROPEAN AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE TRIAL”?",
    "answer": "KAFKA",
    "percentage": "0.8000",
    "response_time": "70.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "222",
    "question": "THE GENERAL NAMED HANNIBAL WAS FROM WHAT CITY?",
    "answer": "CARTHAGE",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "223",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BRITISH ADMIRAL WHO WON THE BATTLE OF TRAFALGAR?",
    "answer": "NELSON",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "6.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "224",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE INDIAN COLLEGE IN PENNSYLVANIA FOR WHICH JIM THORPE PLAYED FOOTBALL?",
    "answer": "CARLISLE",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "66.7"
  },
  {
    "rank": "225",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PLAY IN WHICH ELWOOD P. DOWD IS A CHARACTER?",
    "answer": "HARVEY",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "6.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "226",
    "question": "WHAT FAMOUS KNOT DID ALEXANDER THE GREAT UNDO?",
    "answer": "GORDIAN",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "4.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "227",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE UNSUCCESSFUL AUTO THAT WAS MANUFACTURED BY THE FORD MOTOR COMPANY FROM 1957–1959?",
    "answer": "EDSEL",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "5.2"
  },
  {
    "rank": "228",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SONG WRITER WHO WROTE THE SONG “I LOVE PARIS”?",
    "answer": "PORTER",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "35.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "229",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST AMERICAN AUTHOR TO WIN THE NOBEL PRIZE FOR LITERATURE?",
    "answer": "LEWIS",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "26.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "230",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE INVENTOR OF THE WIRELESS RADIO?",
    "answer": "MARCONI",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "5.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "231",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “AMERICAN GOTHIC”?",
    "answer": "WOOD",
    "percentage": "0.7000",
    "response_time": "18.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "232",
    "question": "IN WHAT PROFESSION WAS EMMETT KELLY?",
    "answer": "CLOWN",
    "percentage": "0.6000",
    "response_time": "3.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "233",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RIVER THAT RUNS THROUGH ROME?",
    "answer": "TIBER",
    "percentage": "0.6000",
    "response_time": "3.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "234",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE POET WHO ORIGINALLY WROTE “DON JUAN”?",
    "answer": "BYRON",
    "percentage": "0.6000",
    "response_time": "15.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "235",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FRENCH AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE STRANGER”?",
    "answer": "CAMUS",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "7.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "236",
    "question": "WHO WAS THE FIRST RULER OF THE HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE?",
    "answer": "CHARLEMAGNE",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "15"
  },
  {
    "rank": "237",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO IS REGARDED AS THE NATIONAL POET OF SCOTLAND?",
    "answer": "BURNS",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "238",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FOOTBALL PLAYER KNOWN AS “THE GALLOPING GHOST”?",
    "answer": "GRANGE",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "6.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "239",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF ROY ROGERS’ HORSE?",
    "answer": "TRIGGER",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "3.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "240",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE NUCLEAR SUBMARINE THAT SUNK IN THE ATLANTIC IN 1963?",
    "answer": "THRESHER",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "42.6"
  },
  {
    "rank": "241",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MAN WHO REMOVED THE THORN FROM THE LION’S PAW IN THE STORY FROM AESOP’S FABLES?",
    "answer": "ANDROCLES",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "23.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "242",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BRIGHTEST STAR IN THE SKY EXCLUDING THE SUN?",
    "answer": "SIRIUS",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "9.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "243",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LAND OF THE GIANTS IN “GULLIVER’S TRAVELS”?",
    "answer": "BROBDINGNAG",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "21.9"
  },
  {
    "rank": "244",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE FEMALE STAR OF THE MOVIE “CASABLANCA”?",
    "answer": "BERGMAN",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "7.4"
  },
  {
    "rank": "245",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR KNOWN AS “THE MAN OF A THOUSAND FACES”?",
    "answer": "CHANEY",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "8.3"
  },
  {
    "rank": "246",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WITH THE HIGHEST LIFETIME BATTING AVERAGE IN THE MAJOR LEAGUES?",
    "answer": "COBB",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "7.8"
  },
  {
    "rank": "247",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR IN THE ROLE OF PERRY MASON ON TELEVISION?",
    "answer": "BURR",
    "percentage": "0.5000",
    "response_time": "12"
  },
  {
    "rank": "248",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MOST POPULAR PIN-UP GIRL OF WORLD WAR II?",
    "answer": "GRABLE",
    "percentage": "0.4000",
    "response_time": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "rank": "249",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST DESERT ON EARTH?",
    "answer": "ANTARTICA",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "250",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE JOCKEY WITH THE MOST LIFETIME WINNERS IN HORSE RACING?",
    "answer": "BAZE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "251",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS THE VOICE OF MR. MAGOO?",
    "answer": "BACKUS",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "252",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED SERGEANT FRIDAY ON “DRAGNET”?",
    "answer": "WEBB",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "253",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED THE FATHER ON THE TELEVISION SHOW “FATHER KNOWS BEST”?",
    "answer": "YOUNG",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "254",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE VENTRILOQUIST WHO PROVIDED THE VOICE FOR CHARLIE MCCARTHY?",
    "answer": "BERGEN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "255",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE CAPTAIN OF THE BRITISH SHIP “BOUNTY” WHEN THE MUTINY OCCURRED?",
    "answer": "BLIGH",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "256",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE INVENTOR OF THE STEAMBOAT “CLERMONT”?",
    "answer": "FULTON",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "257",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF GERMANY’S LARGEST BATTLESHIP THAT WAS SUNK IN WORLD WAR II?",
    "answer": "BISMARCK",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "258",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE JUDGE WHO WAS KNOWN AS “THE LAW WEST OF THE PECOS”?",
    "answer": "BEAN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "259",
    "question": "WHAT IS JOHN KENNETH GALBRAITH’S PROFESSION?",
    "answer": "ECONOMIST",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "260",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE UNION IRONCLAD SHIP THAT FOUGHT THE CONFEDERATE IRONCLAD MERRIMACK?",
    "answer": "MONITOR",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "261",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DOCTOR WHO PERFORMED THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL HUMAN HEART TRANSPLANT?",
    "answer": "BARNARD",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "262",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SAID “I ONLY REGRET THAT I HAVE BUT ONE LIFE TO LOSE FOR MY COUNTRY”?",
    "answer": "HALE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "263",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE PILOT OF THE U-2 SPY PLANE SHOT DOWN OVER RUSSIA IN 1960?",
    "answer": "POWERS",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "264",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED THE SHERIFF IN THE MOVIE “HIGH NOON”?",
    "answer": "COOPER",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "265",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOUNTAIN RANGE THAT SEPARATES ASIA FROM EUROPE?",
    "answer": "URAL",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "266",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO WAS KNOWN AS THE “MANASSA MAULER”?",
    "answer": "DEMPSEY",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "267",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO CREATED THE COMIC STRIP “LI’L ABNER”?",
    "answer": "CAPP",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "268",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WHO PITCHED A PERFECT GAME IN THE 1956 WORLD SERIES?",
    "answer": "LARSEN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "269",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST MAN TO RUN THE MILE IN UNDER FOUR MINUTES?",
    "answer": "BANNISTER",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "270",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “BROTHERS KARAMAZOV”?",
    "answer": "DOSTOYEVSKI",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "271",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO RECEIVED A PULITZER PRIZE FOR HIS WRITINGS ABOUT ABRAHAM LINCOLN?",
    "answer": "SANDBURG",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "272",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO CREATED THE COMIC STRIP “WOODY WOODPECKER”?",
    "answer": "LANTZ",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "273",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE INSTRUMENT USED TO MEASURE WIND SPEED?",
    "answer": "ANEMOMETER",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "274",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “OUR TOWN”?",
    "answer": "WILDER",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "275",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHO MADE A HIT RECORDING OF THE SONG “WHO’S SORRY NOW”?",
    "answer": "FRANCIS",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "276",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CUBAN LEADER THAT CASTRO OVERTHREW?",
    "answer": "BATISTA",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "277",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RUBBER ROLLER ON A TYPEWRITER?",
    "answer": "PLATEN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "278",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST CONFEDERATE MILITARY PRISON DURING THE CIVIL WAR?",
    "answer": "ANDERSONVILLE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "279",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “THE AGONY AND THE ECSTASY”?",
    "answer": "STONE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "280",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF FLASH’S GIRLFRIEND IN THE COMIC STRIP “FLASH GORDON”?",
    "answer": "ARDEN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "281",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FIRST MOVIE TO RECEIVE THE ACADEMY AWARD FOR BEST PICTURE?",
    "answer": "WINGS",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "282",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DISCOVERER OF THE VACCINATION FOR SMALLPOX?",
    "answer": "JENNER",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "283",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOY IN THE BOOK “TREASURE ISLAND”?",
    "answer": "HAWKINS",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "284",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO WON THE BOXING TITLE FROM JOHN L. SULLIVAN?",
    "answer": "CORBETT",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "285",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE SONG “HOW DEEP IS THE OCEAN”?",
    "answer": "BERLIN",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "286",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF BILLY THE KID?",
    "answer": "BONNEY",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "287",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHOSE THEME SONG WAS “WHEN THE BLUE OF THE NIGHT MEETS THE GOLD OF THE DAY”?",
    "answer": "CROSBY",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "288",
    "question": "FROM WHAT MUSICAL IS THE SONG “BAUBLES BANGLES AND BEADS”?",
    "answer": "KISMET",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "289",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED DR. WATSON IN THE SHERLOCK HOLMES SERIES?",
    "answer": "BRUCE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "290",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS MOST RESPONSIBLE FOR PHOTOGRAPHING THE U.S. CIVIL WAR?",
    "answer": "BRADY",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "291",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A NUMBER TWO WOOD IN GOLF?",
    "answer": "BRASSIE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "292",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE POET WHO WROTE THE LINE “INTO EACH LIFE A LITTLE RAIN MUST FALL”?",
    "answer": "LONGFELLOW",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "293",
    "question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF GENE AUTRY’S HORSE?",
    "answer": "CHAMPION",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "294",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE TOWN THROUGH WHICH LADY GODIVA SUPPOSEDLY MADE HER FAMOUS RIDE?",
    "answer": "COVENTRY",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "295",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST WOMAN TO SWIM ACROSS THE ENGLISH CHANNEL?",
    "answer": "EDERLE",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "296",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST FLIER TO FLY SOLO AROUND THE WORLD?",
    "answer": "POST",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "297",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE POEM “IT COULDN’T BE DONE”?",
    "answer": "GUEST",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "298",
    "question": "WHO WAS THE RACEHORSE OF THE YEAR FOR MANY SUCCESSIVE YEARS IN THE 1960S?",
    "answer": "KELSO",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  },
  {
    "rank": "299",
    "question": "WHAT IS THE HIGHEST MOUNTAIN IN SOUTH AMERICA?",
    "answer": "ACONCAGUA",
    "percentage": "0.000",
    "response_time": ""
  }
]